Don't Leave Home is a thriller, mystery film directed by Michael Tully.
An American artist's obsession with a disturbing urban legend leads her to an investigation of
the story's origins at the crumbling estate of a reclusive painter in Ireland.
Melanie Thomas, played by Anna Margaret Hollyman.
Alistair Burke, played by Lalor Roddy.
Shelly, played by Helena Bereen.
Padraig, played by David McSavage.
Conor Callahan, played by Mark Lawrence.
Noreen Callahan, played by Sue Walsh.
Don't Leave Home is a 2018 American horror mystery thriller film written and directed by Michael Tully and
starring Anna Margaret Hollyman, Lalor Roddy, Helena Bereen, David McSavage and Karrie Cox.
The film explores themes of investigation, painter, urban legend, ireland.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.